Hidden Gems is a tv movie, romance, comedy film directed by Maclain Nelson.
While prepping for her sister’s wedding, Addie loses her
grandmother’s ring in the waters of Hawaii.
She hires dive instructor Jack to search for her lost treasure.
They immediately clash with each other when Addie
insists she go on the pursuit with Jack.
Once they come to an agreement, Jack ends up serving as
Addie’s tour guide of the island’s hidden gems.
Addie, played by Hunter King.
Jack, played by Beau Mirchoff.
Kate, played by Eliza Hayes Maher.
Nathan, played by Jordan Matlock.
Betty, played by Diane Sargent.
Robert, played by Brian Connors.
Uncut Gems  is a 2019 American crime thriller film directed by Josh and
Benny Safdie, who wrote the screenplay with Ronald Bronstein.
The film stars Adam Sandler, LaKeith Stanfield, Julia Fox,
Kevin Garnett, Idina Menzel, and Eric Bogosian.
The film tells the story of Howard Ratner, a Jewish-American jeweler and gambling addict who
must retrieve an expensive gem he purchased in order to pay off his debt.
Filming took place from September to November 2018.
The original score is by Daniel Lopatin.
The film premiered at the 46th Telluride Film Festival on August 30, 2019.
A24 gave it a limited release in the United States on
December 13 and a wide release on December 25.
Uncut Gems was a box-office success and received acclaim, especially for Sandler's
against-type performance, which several reviewers called the best of his career.
The film was chosen by the National Board of Review
as one of the top ten films of 2019.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.